Having too much electricity is a strange
problem. I really need help with solar,
but I need help today. Let me show you
what I've installed and then I'll tell
you what's going on. Three big battery
Apex 10 kWs, they're all wired in
parallel. That's going to be producing
131 amps at 230 volts continuous. I got
four big battery Nexus Pros all wired in
parallel. That's going to give me 60 kW
of storage. I have 2625 watt panels, two
groups of 10 wired in series and
connected to the inverters. That'll make
about 40 50 60 kW a day depending on
sunlight. house is running off grid.
We've got all the energy we need and
therein lies the problem. See how full
my batteries are? You see that the sun
is still shining? You cannot charge a
full battery. Initially, I tried to give
the energy back to the Costa Rican
government for free as long as they'd
apply it to Tico accounts who can't pay
their bills. They said no. Governments
are evidently the same worldwide. I'm
stuck with full batteries and sunlight
coming down that can generate energy,
but nothing to use the energy on. Which
brings me to my problem. How does one
mine for Bitcoin? I understand that
mining for Bitcoin just takes
electricity. Problem is that most
people's electricity is very expensive,
but I'm in the unique situation where I
have too much electricity and ample
electricity coming down from God every
day. As you can tell, I am not exactly a
Bitcoin miner, just a redneck with an
iPhone and a badass solar system and I
could use some help here. So, if you are
a Bitcoin mining professional like I'm a
solar professional and you like to come
down here to Costa Rica and help me set
up a Bitcoin mining farm that runs off
the sun so we can take money from the
cyber world and use it to do great
things for planet Earth and humanity.
Holler at your boy Joe. I know you dig
the best.